

NURULLAH ÖZDEMİR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

A senior software developer on more than 15 years of experience with enterprise architecting, implementing and leading software solutions as well as technical leadership for development teams varying from 3 to 20 members, spanning across web also mobile and desktop environments.

**BIRTH**: 1987

### CONTACT

Address: Tekirdağ

Phone: (90) 505 763 73 50

Email: nrlozdemir@gmail.com

# **KEY SKILLS**

JavaScript (ES5+)

Node.js

> React

▶ PHP

> CSS3

SQL (MySQL, Microsoft SQL)

MongoDB

ElasticSearch

> JSON, REST

React Native

➤ HTML5

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**REMOTIFY** 03/2020 - Present

Frontend Developer Full Time

**SAYPR** 02/2019 - 02/2020

React Developer Full Time

**PROCURFY** 09/2018 - 02/2019

JavaScript Developer Full Time

**MN YAZILIM** 08/2012 - 09/2018

Full Stack Developer Full Time

**SPIL GAMES** 11/2009 - 03/2012

Senior PHP Developer Full Time

**KANAL7** 08/2007 - 10/2009

PHP Developer Full Time

**ASUS HOSTING** 07/2005 - 03/2007

Junior Developer Full Time

FREELANCE 09/2003 - 04/2005

Developer

## **EDUCATION**

Dogus University - Software Engineering (Bachelor's Degree)

2020 - 2022 July

**Marmara University - Computer Programming (Associate Degree)** 

2018 - 2020 January

Pamukkale University - Mechanical Engineering (Bachelor's Degree)

2005 - 2007 (Dropped)

Afyonkarahisar Anadolu Öğretmen Lisesi

2001 - 2005

# **LANGUAGES**

English – B2